Guide to the Jean Yeager Papers, 1959-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-1992 and undated
  - 7-Eleven. Undated. 1. Toilet Flush, 2. Frank Fudge Gets Hard, 3. Bob & Frank-Ice/Asphalt, 4. 7 Eleven Beer, 5. Halloween Candy, 6. Bob & Frank Witches…. 7. Watermelons-Two Seeds Talking, 8. Open Memorial Day/Bologna, 9. Walnuts Mountain/Dirty, 10. Glows In The Dark, 11. Dirty Books, 12. Mr. Balloon-6095, 13. Ham & Cheese. Audio tape reel. (Box 22)
  - 7-Eleven. 1984. 1984 7-Eleven Meeting: Production Numbers Only. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Brinkley & Brinkley. 1984. Single Point Responsibility. Umatic. 6:00 (Box 22)
  - Chemical Safety. Undated. VHS. 15:50 (Box 22)
  - Chief Auto Parts. Undated. Hard Part Generic, Basic Generic, Grand Opening Las Vegas, Grand Opening DFW, 25th Anniv. Calif. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Coca-Cola. Undated. Coca-Cola Centennial Heritage Show. VHS. 1:50:08 (Box 22)
  - Frito Lay Inc. 1986. Grab Bags Nashville. VHS. 7:32 (Box 22)
  - Jean W. Yeager. Undated. Change Game. Umatic. 6:40 (Box 22)
  - Jean W. Yeager. 1989. Change Game AMC Video 11-05-89. VHS. 6:40 (Box 22)
  - Jean W. Yeager. 1987. Children of Peace Rehearsal 12/12/87, Performance 13th 2:30 PM. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Jean W. Yeager. Undated. Lexicon Creative Writing Service--Change Game. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Jean W. Yeager. Undated. Lexicon Creative Writing Service--Patton. VHS. (Box 22)
  - K.W. Tunnell Co., Inc. Undated. Executive Seminar Series- How to Become and Stay a World Class Competitor. VHS. 15:00 (Box 22)
  - K.W. Tunnell Co., Inc. 1992. Executive Seminar Series- Managing Culture Change, Conversation. VHS. (Box 22)
  - K.W. Tunnell Co., Inc. Undated. Executive Seminar Series- Managing Culture Shock. VHS. 1:16 (Box 22)
  - K.W. Tunnell Co., Inc. 1992. John Plant/Raw Footage. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Merrill Lynch. Undated. Patton. VHS. 7:50 (Box 22)
  - Network Television. Undated. 1. Chunky Burrito, 2. Breakfast Product Cluster (anamatic), 3. Big Gulp Price comparison, 4. Image/Slurpee (anamatic). Umatic. (Box 22)
  - Pacific Reality Corporation. Undated. People. Umatic. 12:36 (Box 22)
  - Radio Shack. 1981-1986. Radio Shack Xmas Spots. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Radio Shack. Undated. The Model 100 Seminar- A Day In The Life Of The Model 100. VHS. 15:00 (Box 22)
  - Randy Thurman/KWT. 1992. Finished. VHS. (Box 22)
  - Sales Meeting Film. 1988. People's Choice. VHS. 34:40 (Box 22)
  - The Southland Corporation. 1986. 1. Franchise Group Insurance 16:24, 2. More Than A Job 14:03, First Day Benefits 13:38. VHS. 44:05 (Box 22)
  - The Southland Corporation. Undated. Buena Vista. VHS. 5:40 (Box 22)
  - The Southland Corporation. Undated. Dream '84 -MDA. VHS. 12:50 (Box 22)
  - The Southland Corporation. Undated. First Day Benefits. VHS. 17:00 (Box 23)
  - The Southland Corporation. 1984. First Day Benefits. VHS. 22:40 (Box 23)
  - The Southland Corporation. Undated. More Than A Job. VHS. 12:50 (Box 23)
  - The Southland Corporation. Undated. Our Gift To You. VHS. 11:25 (Box 23)
  - The Southland Corporation. 1987. Specialty Retailing. VHS. 7:15 (Box 23)
  - TM Communications. 1984. NAB Show 1984. VHS. 32:00 (Box 23)
  - Window Dub. 1992. Wordsmiths. VHS. 1:40 (Box 23)